Please contact turkision@gmail.com for any inquiries
No living being was harmed during the
filming of this series.
Episode 106
- After a day -
This palace...
is the heart of the state.
However, Sultan İsmihan...
thinks she will do what she wants in
our lands as she does in her palace.
We will not allow it.
Now, she will unite with our
enemies to strike us.
You didn't liberate Kantakuzanos in vain.
She must cooperate with him.
Her eyes were blinded by her greed.
This woman might put Olof
under her command.
We won't let her do that.
Her position gives her great power and for
that reason, we have to kill her in order to stop her.
No.
Her position and greed make her arrogant.
This is her weak point.
We will attack her from this weak point.
Then, I had better have them prepare the
presents...
to deceive her.
She won't be fooled by this.
We need something bigger than this.
Will we kiss her hand and obey, father?
She will not be convinced otherwise.
We will do what is necessary.
What are we going to do
after stopping her, father?
What we always do.
One enemy goes and another comes.
But the homeland of the
Turks remains forever.
We will continue the conquests.
Saruca is after Sultan İsmihan.
He will tell us who she meets and sees.
You're talking about
enemy campaigns but...
What about a friend?
We can't defeat the enemy if
the brothers don't unite, Bala
And no one can close
these cracks except a brother.
Turgut Bey will certainly be with us.
What if he doesn't, my Bey?
İnegöl Castle
We sensed your absence from
headquarters, Turgut Bey.
But you know that going out on
the path of conquest is by faith.
No need to convince
anyone of that.
Do you teach that to us, Konur?
No.
Your absence...
Do not blame me for my absence.
I fought tirelessly all these years.
I did not come to talk about the past.
You have a problem with
my Bey, solve it with him.
I have come to take our
catapults at his command.
Okay.
Where are you now, Konur?
İnegöl.
The catapults you're talking about
are the ones that took Inegol.
These catapults are the keys
to the castle, as they say.
They are mine just like İnegöl.
It is up to me to handle it.
No.
Will you make yourself priority?
Nothing could be more important
than my calling.
Everything I do is to please Allah.
My concern is justice, Konur, don't
you see that?
Do you relieve yourself like that?
Did greed blind your
eyes to this degree?
No, you got it wrong, Konur.
Seeking the truth is not greedy.
I haven't spoken all these years.
How Osman Bey treated me is clear.
You're
wrong, Turgut Bey.
I haven't chosen my path yet, Konur.
Go to headquarters.
I will inform Osman Bey. of my decision
Take Konur to the castle exit.
The wound in my chest has not yet healed.
Don't open another wound, Turgut Bey.
We are waiting for good news from you.
We have the same goal with people like
İsmihan Sultan.
But what makes us different from them...
is our concern.
Their goal is gold and royalty.
As for us, our goal is the homeland.
They want the sword for power.
What about us?
We want it to spread justice.
They want the position, the chair,
and the throne for their vanity.
But we want it in order to rule justly.
This is the difference between us.
And what makes us strong...
is this.
So let's crush the enemy with this power.
The enemy fronts will separate now.
The enemies
are sharpening their teeth against us.
But we are not united now.
For this reason, we will
not crush anyone.
We'll be smart.
Malhun Hatun.
Go to the Mother Sultan with your retinue.
And give her our best gifts.
Show her our sincerity.
If that will stop it...
she will find no better gift
than our faithfulness, my Bey.
You are right.
Bala, you will come with me
to Köprühisar headquarters.
Me and the female warriors
are behind you, my Bey.
Olof and Kantakuzenos...
And İsmihan Sultan.
They'll all think we stopped.
But we will never stop.
İsmihan Sultan and Kantakuzenos.
They will move together.
If we move before the enemy...
we will be victorious.
It's time to make a deal to confront
Osman, who's manipulating our borders.
What worries you?
Why ally with me instead
of allying with one of you?
He who does not
oppose us is of us, Kantakuzenos.
Osman grew up under the wings
of the Seljuk Empire.
But he acted according to his whims.
He did not stop at acting
according to his whims.
He even clawed his bloody
hand to Constantinople.
I know everything.
The weaker the state is...
The traitors' voice becomes loud.
So let's cut that sound out.
Don't you want to hear our terms?
You will not attack the Turks
or any Turkish village.
My war is with Osman only.
No Turk will be harmed who
does not draw the sword against me.
As long as our goal is the same...
Then you know I'll have your back, Kantakuzenos...
to have the throne of Byzantium
that you want the most.
I am grateful, Your Majesty,
but I am no longer the heir...
rather, I own the throne.
The Emperor is so ill that he
can't use his powers.
For this reason, I will run
the empire on his behalf.
Our strength towards Osman increases.
If we can find out what
Osman is after...
The power we possess will double.
He is looking for a new conquest.
It could be Koyunhisar...
It could be Çadırlı.
Or Köprühisar.
He must want to take one of them.
Who knows what you are up to.
I knew it wouldn't stop
after taking Marmaracık.
We must know his campaign
in advance and stop him.
Come here.
Don't worry, Kantakuzenos.
Osman has been watching me for a while.
What does this mean?
Do you suspect us?
He must not be made aware
of our agreement in any way
Osman is trying to stop me.
You agree with
him to stop my Bey.
But you can not stop
those who take the path of truth.
Unfortunately, the dead can not
speak, Kantakuzenos.
Are you ready to stand by me as I destroy
Osman's lands?
What are we waiting for
to attack them, Olof?
We are waiting for the
right time, brother.
Our patience will be the
key to our victory this time.
There are people coming.
In addition to our agreement with
those who live with our enemy...
- Tell me where to attack.
- You're hasty like Osman, Olof.
Where is Osman after now?
We know that Osman seeks
after the conquests, but...
We don't know where he will attack.
But we will know for sure.
And when we know, we will hit him
before he reaches his goal.
Why did you come now when you don't know
where Osman will attack?
I came to tell you what we're going to do.
We will wreak havoc inside and you'll
attack that place where we wreak havoc.
Wait for word from me and
don't move until then.
I'm not a hunting dog, Bayındır.
Tell your Sultan that she
will grant me what I want.
What do you want but war and blood?
I want a home and land.
Lands that do not belong to the
Seljuk state nor to Byzantium.
Lands that are for me and
my brothers only.
When the war is completely over, Marmaracık
and its surroundings will belong to me.
Only me.
I don't have the right to
grant you this, however...
I can convince Sultan.
It is not enough to convince her.
Next time you come, you will bring me a
document bearing the Sultan's seal...
stating that Marmaracık
Castle belongs to me.
Otherwise, I'll cut off your head then.
Consider cutting off Osman's
head and make it happen.
My Sultan will give you the power
greater than Marmaracık.
Wait for the news.
Köprühisar headquarters
There is no news of Turgut Bey.
What will we tell Osman Bey
if Turgut Bey does not come?
We've fought many wars over the years
together with him, and he can't do such a thing.
Brothers, we were together
also in Marmaracık.
- He shouldn't.
- He won't, but -
Wasn't it about the castle, Konur?
It shouldn't be about
the castle, Cerkutay.
Are you saying that the person we
depend on has turned his back on us ?
Turgut Bey is heartbroken.
What will someone do when
his heart is broken?
He will attack the
infidels and find his medicine.
Turgut Bey knows this and will come
It is up to him in the end but what we
need are catapults and siege weapons.
It shouldn't look like he put his
hand on them like that.
It really shouldn't happen.
But he will take his weapon
and bring his men to join us.
What will Osman Bey
do if he doesn't give us the catapults?
Osman Bey is coming.
- Where are the catapults?
- Turgut Bey didn't give us the catapults.
Turgut.
İnegöl Castle
Mother İsmihan Sultan is coming!
You have honored İnegöl with
your presence, Mother Sultan.
But we weren't waiting for you.
We were waiting for you
to tell us before you came.
What happened?
When did the Seljuks send word when
they came to their property, Turgut Bey?
Get out.
Many things have changed since
we took our hands off the border.
It is certain Osman Bey's greatest
possession is İnegol Castle.
Do you want me to say
that İnegol Castle is mine?
Do you want me to stand against Osman Bey?
He will also be angry with me.
I will be angry with him and join your ranks.
Is this what you are aiming for?
Mother Sultan,
this issue is a matter between brothers.
And if you're looking for a traitor
against Osman Bey, don't come to me.
Because there is no traitor here.
You have misunderstood me, Turgut Bey.
I just wanted to see Osman Bey's property.
And you are one of the
Beys of Osman Bey.
You're nothing other
than his shadow.
Whoever stays in the shadows
gets used to the darkness.
Mother Sultan.
I'm keeping a few of my warriors
on the way to İnegol Castle.
I have buried many of
my brave men in the dirt.
And I'm the one who raised
the flag over İnegol Castle.
I heard it, Turgut Bey.
You lost your wife and son.
And you did not betray Osman Bey
despite everything you've been through.
For this reason, I want you to be
at my side as a Bey.
You are different from Osman Bey.
You just want your right.
You only want the price
for the blood you shed.
What did Osman Bey
do when you claimed your right?
Didn't he ignore it, Turgut Bey?
Where is the price of the
blood your heroes shed?
Come work with me, Turgut.
Have a position in the state.
Think deeply.
And we will meet again.
Turgut Bey.
You deserve more.
So then, Turgut!
You betrayed me in spite of our
brotherhood for the sake of a castle.
I forgive those who betray me, however...
but you betrayed our calling.
I will never forgive those who exchange
the call of Islam for the idol of selfishness.
Now...
Everyone will check his heart out.
You will see what is in your hearts.
Leave if you have the same selfishness.
Leave if you sit at
Satan's table and works with his friends.
Leave if you do not have the
courage in your heart.
Instead of going with the scared ones...
I had better go alone.
We are with you, Osman Bey.
Your calling is our calling.
If the catapults
don't come till evening...
I shall behead Turgut Bey!
Yenişehir
Thank you.
May your job be easy, Alçiçek.
Thank you, Aktemur Bey.
Aktemur.
You shouldn't have set your eyes
on what's mine, Aktemur.
Your blood became lawful for me.
I must act quickly before
the bird flies out of its nest.
- Hüseyin.
- Yes, my Bey.
- Wait here.
- Yes, sir.
- May your job be easy, Bengi Hatun.
- Thank you, Bayındır Bey.
I'd like to talk to you if you're a little free.
Take Esma with you and bring back the
goods that the merchants have prepared.
So, Bayındır Bey?
What is so secretive?
It is a matter of good, a matter of good, but...
I know this is not the
right place, but...
It will get more difficult if we
wait any longer.
Speak clearly, what are you saying?
Oh, Bengi Hatun.
We have respected each
other for a long time.
Öktem Bey knows me, you
know me, and I know you both.
What I want to say is...
that I want to propose to
your daughter, Alçiçek.
What are you
saying, Bayındır Bey?
You haven't said anything
like that until now.
Where did you get this from now?
Mother Sultan...
She continues to say that she will never
leave here before my wedding ceremony.
I passed the age of marriage.
So I thought and decided...
and I said, "Why don't you and Öktem Bey
be relatives?"
I hope I didn't make a
mistake by doing this.
Not at all, Bayındır Bey.
But you should talk to Öktem Bey, not me.
Of course, of course.
...of course I'll talk to him, but...
I wanted to tell you this, Bengi Hatun.
Öktem Bey doesn't care as much about
anyone's words in this world as yours.
Inform him of my intention.
We'll come to ask for the girl
at a time that suits you.
And who knows, maybe...
We come with the Mother
Sultan to ask for Alçiçek.
Stay healthy and well.
Where are you going now, Alçiçek?
Koyunhisar, Köprühisar, Lefka and Çadırlı.
These are the places that
Osman is likely to attack.
Lefka is the strongest place among them.
He will not attack that place.
But the rest of the places...
They increased their reserves in the rest
of the castles when they lost Marmaracık.
That is not enough.
I'll
go to Köprühisar, and you go to Çadırlı.
And if Osman attacks
places other than this...
we'll unite our forces at the Black Stone
site and advance from there.
It will make our work easier if Bayındır knows
where Osman will attack before him.
The traitor on Osman's side.
- Bayındır will finish him.
- Good.
I must be sure of your loyalty
to me now, Olof.
What do you want?
I want you to leave paganism and become a Christian
while we fight these Muslim barbarians.
Then I will be sure of your
faithfulness to me.
My grandparents left their religion.
And they converted
to Christianity.
But I will not promise you this.
If you succeed in this...
You will become a loyal Byzantium soldier.
Then you will have everything you desire.
I showed my loyalty to
Byzantium by sacrificing my brother.
But I will think about this.
My Bey.
To get past the walls, we need
the catapults in İnegöl.
You say, the conquest does not take
place without the catapults, right?
We'll take those catapults.
Either by virtue or by force.
Turgut Bey is coming.
I told you he would come.
He really came.
Long live, Turgut Bey.
Come on.
Söğüt
Our eyes and ears in Yenişehir are
reliable, my Sultan.
No bird could fly there without
our knowledge.
Hello there, Frigg.
Obviously, our mutual friends
have introduced you to me for a long time.
Mother Sultan.
Here, Mother Sultan.
The snake called Frigg is that woman.
She fooled everyone with her
angelic face, however...
It was revealed in front of me.
There is no better weapon used
than a powerful snake, Bayındır.
We will move together towards
our common goals.
After destroying Osman...
You will live freely as Frigg.
As long as our interests are the same...
Then you can be sure that I
will side with you, Mother Sultan.
I don't need to be so sure, Frigg.
But, you should be sure.
So that this beautiful head of yours will remain
upon your body as long as you are at my command.
Now hear me well.
I've been off balance ever
since Öktem said it.
My dreams were shattered there.
Are your dreams shattered
for the first time?
We went through all
those defeats together.
As you said, you left the man who never
left you alone even in defeats alone.
You chose this.
You pushed me there by choosing a man who
was not with us in the conquest.
A friend is known in distress.
We went through a lot of things.
You did not object to my
choices in those days.
Now, you fail even though you passed
in difficult times.
How long have you been
dreaming of royalty?
Since the blood of my warriors spilled on the
soil in the conquests for years.
Didn't Öktem's blood spill?
You gave possession to whoever
was not present at the conquest.
I have always been by your side.
You chose this.
That's your decision.
You have no place with us.
Yes.
I only brought the catapults.
May Allah prolong your life, Alps.
And let your path be open.
The path of one who seeks
conquest is always open.
The one who goes into the dark is you.
Let your path be open.
Who choses the white path..
and who chooses the black
will certainly be clarified.
He who does not see his
mistake has no place among us.
I...
I leave you because of my mercy...
to see the truth.
If you will not see the truth...
The truth is quite clear.
You made a mistake in choosing the Beys
in the conquest.
If I'm wrong, it's my fault.
But you...
You abandon your case
because of this mistake.
This issue can not bear to remain
between you and yourself.
You are giving an opportunity
to seduce Satan.
I don't fight, Osman Bey.
I will always pursue this blessed calling.
I will walk alone if necessary.
But you, if you consider that I have given up
on this cause because I am not behind you...
It is because of your own greed.
You are trying to walk alone the path
we should walk together.
Let your path be open.
Come on.
We'll see many victories together, Frigg.
I will not show modesty in
this matter, İsmihan Sultan.
However, do not shy away from humility.
Your life is between my lips.
But our priority is the lives of our
common enemies, right?
Malhu Hatun has come, Mother Sultan.
And she would like to see you.
Come on.
What a pleasant visit, Malhun Hatun.
We wante to visit, İsmihan Sultan.
Sorry.
Unaware of your arrival, we could not
properly accommodate you in our palace.
But you obviously spent
a lot of time in Yenişehir.
So much so that you got to know Marta.
We met, yes.
I never expected to find someone so good
and of such high quality here.
Marta is your white face, Malhun Hatun.
I'm trying to be nice to you, lady.
How happy I am if I make you happy.
Thank you.
From now on, I always want to
see you by my side.
And now permission is yours.
Avcı will take care of you as he should.
Marta has amazingly good taste.
And she's noble.
Unlike you.
But I understand you very well.
Even if you leave the tribe...
The tribe is in you.
I excuse your audacity in not hosting the
Mother Sultan properly because of your ignorance.
These are the pains of
transition to civilisation.
You'll get used to it, Malhun Hatun
I have no doubt that you will
deserve where you are in time.
Mother Sultan.
We know that our judgment derives from
the strength we got from Konya.
And you are not a guest.
You're the owner of the place for us.
We started nervously at the palace.
I'm glad to know it won't last.
Because I don't want you to get
hurt over small issues.
Sorry, Mother Sultan.
Osman Bey has sent these gifts as a sign
of our shame and as a sign of our loyalty to you.
We are glad you accepted it.
My happiness is linked to the happiness of
my people and yours.
Of course, I take it, Malhun Hatun.
Gladly.
You won't agree.
My mom won't let Bayındır to ask for me.
No, she will.
If Bayındır convinces her, she'll let him.
Is Aktemur coming?
I told him, he will come.
But you grieve in vain, Alçiçek Hatun.
I told you, Öktem Bey won't find
a better son-in-law than Aktemur.
My mother does not want him.
Don't you know my mom?
She'll do whatever it takes
and convince my father.
Alçiçek.
Esma, go.
If my mother asks
anything, distract her.
I told you.
We will be miserable together.
It's time to be miserable, Aktemur.
What happened, Alçiçek?
What do you mean?
Esma heard that...
one of them went to my mother
and asked for me.
From? And what did he ask, Alçiçek?
What do you say?
What do you not understand?
One of the Beys
wants to marry me.
I'm telling you, Aktemur.
Say it, who is he?
What are you going to do?
This is not our problem.
I told you who he is, Alçiçek?
Who is looking at my sweetheart
with a deviant eye?
Tell me.
Bayındır Bey.
He said the name of the Mother Sultan...
to convince my mother.
If my mother is convinced, my
father will be convinced, Aktemur.
Bayındır.
I will find him.
Stop, wait.
It can't be like this, Aktemur.
I tell you that İsmihan
Sultan is behind him.
You will bring yourself trouble.
What do we do now?
I'm going to root this out
today, Alçiçek Hatun.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
We'll go to my uncle's.
Aktemur.
I will end you.
Come on, Hüseyin, let's go
after them quickly.
You will attack the enemy.
What's the matter?
Go!
Come.
You are...
You will strike as if you
were hitting the enemy.
How are you doing this?
We'll go to war, war!
You will die for one mistake!
- Osman.
- I'm talking to you.
My Osman!
My Osman, come and rest a bit.
Drink water.
Come on, come on, my dear Osman.
Come on.
Tell me, my dear Osman.
Is Turgut Bey the reason for
all your anger, dear Osman?
The greed of the world has entered
among my warriors and Beys.
Turgut, who fought us shoulder to shoulder
all those years ago...
deviates from our path now for just
a castle.
Bala, is there anything more
dangerous than this?
Tell me, is there?
Inshallah, you will overcome
this danger, my dear Osman.
Well, what about my Beys and my Alps?
What if they were defeated in front of these ambitions?
What will happen then?
We'll get through
this, my dear Osman.
We will get over this, Inshallah.
We will pray to Allah.
And we'll be careful.
We will not fall into the
temptation of Satan, Inshallah.
It's true what you say.
I was determined to walk this path
even if I was alone.
Dear Osman, you are not alone.
Know that I will follow
you wherever you go.
Point to the target and
we will march to it.
It is enough for us to walk together
toward conquest and martyrdom.
I know, dear Bala, I know.
I consider that you and I are one.
But what we saw today...
It shows us that we are not alone
on this road anymore.
For this reason, we have to do a lot.
Lots.
My Bey, Aktemur Bey
and Alçiçek Hatun are coming.
Are they coming here?
What is this, Osman Bey?
You have set the
military headquarters here.
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam.
Look at Aktemur.
He tells his uncle about it at once.
Now they will ask for the girl at once.
Is it possible that I leave
you what is mine?
Hüseyin.
- My Bey.
- Let's go right away.
If they see us here, they
won't leave us alive.
It is true what you say, my Bey.
Come on.
Bala.
Let's go, Alçiçek.
It seemed like it mattered as you brought
Alçiçek here.
Yes, it is important.
My uncle.
Didn't you ask me if Alçiçek
loves me, too?
I knew the answer to that question.
Her answer is clear, son.
We all saw it and believed it.
But now there is something else.
One of the Beys intends to
propose to Alçiçek for marriage.
Who is he?
Bayındır.
He said it himself.
He says that İsmihan Sultan
is standing behind him.
Bayındır.
Alçiçek, forgive me.
That slap...
When I saw Aktemur in that
state with blood all over him...
I forgive you for my right.
Whoever was in your position
would have done the same.
I'm not upset.
But I would like to
join the women warriors.
Thank you.
Let's do your wedding.
Then we will discuss this.
I'm not worried about
my father, but my mother.
You know she doesn't get along
with Ayşe Hatun.
Don't be afraid, these are
small things in front of love.
They will all be resolved.
His intention is to
make a trouble.
He wants to unite with Öktem
and prevail before us.
Uncle, I kept you busy with my problems
before such an important conquest.
No, my nephew.
You have opened a heart, is this possible?
We'll go ask for the girl.
And I will do my duty as your uncle.
My Bey.
There is another issue yet.
They spread men everywhere.
They obviously know
you're not in Yenişehir.
They are looking for you.
Well then, let's go and show
them ourselves.
And we ask for our girl.
Bala.
We will go to Yenişehir.
We'll go to Marmaracık to ask for Alçiçek
before the conquest.
Oğuz Alp.
- My Bey.
- Send word to Öktem Bey.
We're coming to him
for something good.
Your command, my Beyç
Son.
Bala.
Come on.
We now know the location of
Osman's military headquarters.
He can't take a step in Köpruhisar
without this headquarters.
Nice.
Very nice.
But you don't seem
to get too excited about it, Bayındır.
Not at all.
Of course I am happy.
We found Osman's hole, of
course I'm happy.
However...
There is another issue yet.
Mother Sultan.
Osman will ask for a girl for his nephew.
What do we have to do with this?
Yes, you're right but...
Osman will ask for Öktem
Bey's daughter, Alçiçek Hatun.
This marriage will
strengthen Osman internally.
And he will gather all the tribes.
And there is Marmaracık, of course.
Is that what's bothering you, Bayındır?
You...
I want Alçiçek Hatun
for myself, my Sultan.
Obviously, Osman will act
quickly and ask for the girl.
Let's go before him and take
the girl, my Sultan.
Love matters.
I understood.
Alçiçek will be your wife.
This is what Mother Sultan ordered.
May Allah be pleased with you, my Sultan.
Stand up, Bayındır.
Stand up.
And send word to Olof and
the others at once.
Describe to them the location of the
military headquarters well.
And tell them to destroy that headquarters...
with whoever is inside it.
And Osman too?
An army without a leader is considered
non-existent, Bayındır.
We must finish off Osman
and scatter his army.
And I thought of something different
for Osman.
He and his dear wife Malhun
will be my guests tonight.
You, in the meantime, will be a
man engaged to Alçiçek.
My Sultan, I will send
Hüseyin to Olof but...
Olof doesn't do it for nothing.
He wants Marmaracık.
They must ask for it.
Greedy creatures.
Tell them not to worry.
They will get what they want.
What happened, my Bey?
Is there a problem before the conquest?
Good, good.
We'll conquer a heart before the castle.
Do the preparations.
We'll ask for Alçiçek for Aktemur.
I'm so happy, Aktemur.
Ayşe Hatun.
We sent word like this
without asking you, however...
excuse us.
It's okay, my Bey.
Whatever we say is not important.
If Gündüz was alive, he would have
made the decision you made.
May Allah bless you.
Come on, let's get ready.
I said it.
Mother.
Aktemur Bey, I'm happy for you.
Don't act like that, mother.
Aktemur.
How could you do such a thing without
consulting me and taking my permission?
You've run me over
with your behaviour.
What are you saying, mother?
Don't act like that.
- I was...
- No!
Go and ask for her with your uncle.
I will not go to that palace.
Bayındır.
He will ask for Alçiçek.
I can't live without her, mother.
I was forced.
Is it reasonable for me to do something
like this without your permission?
Don't leave me alone on a day like this
Aktemur.
You say you can't live without her.
Do you really love her that much?
And what about her?
Does she love you too?
Or else why would she run to notify me?
She also loves me as much as
I love her, mother!
You will come, right?
Son, I see your love.
But I don't believe in that girl's love.
A lover never neglects her beloved,
Aktemur.
Don't you trust my words, Mother.
I'm telling you, Alcicek loves me back!
I see love in her eyes.
Come on, mother!
Don't leave me alone on a day like this.
Marmaracik Castle
You said they had
no intention of doing so.
Osman Bey is coming to ask for Alcicek.
You wouldn't permit, would you Oktem?
It's Osman Bey!
Osman Bey, the Bey of these lands!
The Bey who made Marmaracik home!
Osman Bey!
What will I tell him when
he stands on my doorstep?
If Alcicek agrees,
there's nothing else to do.
I told you not to permit, Oktem!
I will, Hatun!
You will not!
Oktem, I won't give my daughter
to Subasi.
Those Kayis killed my brother.
We suffered due to them!
I can't forget that.
Enough, Hatun, enough!
I will not listen to you!
I'll give Alcicek to Aktemur!
Attention, Mother Isfihan Sultan.
Will you, Oktem Bey?
What if I ask for Alcicek?
What will you do then?
Will you give your daughter to Osman Bey
and not to me?
Yenisehir
Osman Bey's Mansion
Ulgen Hatun.
I'm calling you Ulgen Hatun!
Don't you hear me?
I am deaf.
Deaf!
Ulgen Hatun.
I didn't want to offend you.
Forgive me.
"I didn't want to offend you"
You made fun of me, all those people knew
you could hear. You made fun of me!
Who knows what they thought about me!?
From now on, I will not see or hear you
Cerkutay Alp!
Aren't you going to give me food?
I will kill you, I swear to Allah!
No!
Are you eating food Cerkutay, huh?
- Hi sister Ulgen.
- Welcome.
Give me some food, will you?
Sure, sure
I'm hungry.
Great job, sister Ulgen.
- Enjoy it.
- Enjoy it brother.
You enjoy too, brother.
Don't do this to me.
This amount can't satisfy anyone!
Enjoy it Boran Alp!
Enjoy it!
You'll eat as much as I give you,
there's no more!
Are you telling me to stay hungry?
From now on, eating your fill
is haram for you!
I'll leave then!
Look, I said I'll go!
Who am I talking to?
No.
I am deaf, deaf.
I am deaf.
- I am leaving.
- Go away.
- Leaving hungry.
- May your fight be blessed. Go.
- I am going to war.
- Go wherever you go.
I can't help it.
How am I...
...going to stab my enemies in the heart!
Enemies will stab you instead!
Think about what you have done to me!
Tawbah tawbah!
I didn't mean this! My Allah!
Ah Cerkutay Ah!
What have I done to deserve this?
Cerkutay.
What are you doing brother?
Yes brother, what am I doing?
I think I lost my mind because of hunger.
She doesn't give me food.
Let me, brother.
Ah Cerkutay ah!
Ah, they'll defeat me brother Boran!
What am I going to do, brother?
They'll defeat me brother Boran!
What can I say, Ismahan Sultan?
You tied me up.
I didn't do anything, Oktem Bey.
Before Osman Bey,
Bayindir Bey knocked your door.
And now, as being the mother Sultan...
...I ask for your daughter.
I was glad to be Oktem Bey's relative.
But it seems like he doesn't want us.
Not at all, Bayindir Bey.
It is not like how you think.
We trust you completely.
Don't we, Oktem Bey?
Can we find someone
better than Bayindir Bey?
Right.
Right, but...
- Osman Bey...
- Osman Bey is such a hard head.
He is a rebel.
You all know what the end of this rebellion is.
I mean, Osman Bey is present today
but he may not be tomorrow.
But we are here forever, Oktem Bey.
And I support Bayindir Bey.
First of all...
I have to ask Alcicek.
Of course you will, Oktem Bey.
Of course you will but...
If Alcicek is as smart as her mother...
...she must know the answer.
Alcicek's answer is apparent,
Ismihan Sultan.
Alcicek will agree.
You're too late, Aktemur.
You are too late!
Welcome.
By Allah's command and in accordance with
the tradition of the Messenger of Allah...
...we ask your daughter Alcicek
in marriage with Bayindir Bey.
Osman Bey.
What's happening here?
Oktem Bey.
Haven't we informed you?
What is this situation?
You tell us what is happening, Osman Bey!
Entering without permission.
We abode by the tradition.
We sent the news before we came.
Apparently, you are the one who came
without informing, Isfahan Sultan.
I don't have to inform my people and
my land before visiting them!
I asked a question for you, Oktem Bey.
What is your answer?
Oktem Bey invited us to hear this answer.
Say it then. Say it.
Osman Bey.
- We didn't know.
- Oktem Bey is right.
We are here for something good.
We came and asked for marriage.
And we will get what we want, Inshallah.
Am I right, Oktem Bey?
I give my daughter to Bayindir Bey.
Congratulations.
Oktem Bey, we came here to open hearts.
We came to establish a family.
It certainly won't be
difficult for us to return.
Does Alcicek consent to this?
Her mother is here and her father is here.
We are not giving her by force,
are we Osman Bey?
Do you think we are tyrant?
Shame on you Osman Bey.
How could someone be forced
to do such a good thing.
Now if you excuse,
we'll talk about our wedding.
Also, I want to host you
with your family and Beys...
...in Soguthan.
Sultan Aladdin has important news.
Aktemur.
- Alcicek, I...
- Shut up.
Listen to me.
I do not want Bayindir.
Do you...
Do you still want to marry me?
I don't just want to marry you.
I want to grow old and die with you Alcicek!
There is only one solution now.
We have to elope tomorrow!
I'll come, Alcicek Hatun.
I will come to get you out of this hell
even if my hands are covered in blood!
I'll wait for you under the crooked tree
at Camlik.
Come on, they'll understand.
Kopru Hisar.
The walls are covered.
Trenches were dug around the castle.
Now whoever tries to attack can't
get past the walls, Olof
Nice.
Deploy the soldiers.
Nobody shall sleep.
Bayindir's man has come, Olof.
Let him in.
Bayindir Bey sent me.
This shows the location
of Osman's headquarters
So what?
So, this is the order of Ismihan Sultan.
She orders you to destroy the headquarters
tomorrow night.
In return of what?
Sultan says you will have
something in return.
The headquarters is near Kopruhisar.
At Taspinar.
If you fail destroy the headquarters.
You will end up like
how you did in Marmaracik.
Leave him Dan.
I will kill thousands of
birds with one stone.
I will both get Marmaracik back...
...and take everything Osman has.
Do you think Osman Bey
will come tomorrow night?
He will, Avci.
He will.
They obeyed me today.
No one can refuse
the invitation of Mother Sultan.
- Are the gifts ready?
- Yes my Sultan.
I have prepared two white horses for
Orhan and Aladdin Beys.
Two horses?
No, Avci, not two horses.
We'll gift them one horse.
What is the greatest weakness of mothers?
Why am I here, Avci?
Because I am a mother.
And the biggest weakness of
Bala Hatun and Malhun Hatun...
....is their children.
They will fall out with each other...
Orhan and Aladdin issue...
...will help us set
Hatuns against each other.
I will do as you say, my Sultan.
This white horse...
... will run to crush Osman Bey's
dreams of establishing a state.
Ismihan Sultan does not interfere
in this for nothing.
She thinks we want to dominate Oktem Bey
by taking Alcicek.
For this reason, she wants to interfere.
Be patient.
I'll have that girl for you.
I had promised your father that I would
arrange your wedding ceremony.
- Insahllah my Bey.
- Inshallah.
Bayindir has been following Ismihan
like a dog since she arrived.
Obviously, those two set up this plan.
Ismihan Sultan will take Oktem Bey away
from us by using Bayindir Bey.
Saruca, still no news from him.
- Sen alps.
- As you order, my Bey.
The enemy is increasing and
the conquests are difficult
Now things get really complicated, my Bey.
Like you said, Malhun,
it's really difficult.
From now on, difficulty has no importance.
Here is the headquarters!
Here is the castle we will conquer!
Neither the large number of the enemy....
...nor us being few in number
won't make us step back!
With the permission of our Allah...
...Kopru Hisar will be ours by sunrise.
Insha'Allah.
Sogut.
I want to host Sheik Edebali.
He is the light of Oghuz.
Osman's biggest weakness.
If we turn off that light...
...then we'll leave Osman in the dark.
- Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too my Sheik.
You brought pleasure.
You enlightened our home with your light.
Not at all.
Please.
In the name of of Allah
the Merciful the Compassionate.
Welcome, Ismihan Sultan.
May your sudden arrival be a means of good.
Wehave nothing to do with evil, my Sheik.
Our intention is to do good deeds.
And that the people benefit from this good.
If your heart is the mirror
of your tongue...
...there should be nothing to worry about,
Ismihan Sultan.
Tell me, why did you come?
I am starting to think that
our arrival in Sogut bothers you.
This makes me sad, my sheik.
Not at all.
Why would we be bothered?
Sogut belongs to Allah,
like the rest of the world.
Your presence is neither
grace nor distress for us.
But your presence is a grace for us.
I want to talk to you privately.
About the current situation
of the Islamic world.
Share my worries a little bit.
You opened your table for me.
And if you are sincere in your concerns,
then you will surely find a cure.
Has it always been like this?
Has the union of Muslims been so difficult
all the time?
Staying away from arrogance?
It has been always difficult.
Tests for Muslims are always difficult.
We experienecd difficulty because of the
hypocrites who concealed themselves.
They are more dangerous than the enemy.
The greatest harm to the Islamic world
was caused by the hypocrites.
How do they do this, my sheikh?
Those seem to be from us, however...
They are our biggest enemies.
They sit at our table
And they invite us to their table, however...
...The dagger in their hand plans
to stab us in the back.
But we know that
all the hypocrites will definitely
get their share of the
Prophet's curse for them
I did not know that our beloved Prophet
had cursed anyone.
This means that he suffered a lot.
So he cursed them.
I want to know the reason for that.
At one point...
A messenger from Necid's deserts came
to our Prophet.
He asked for Hafizs to tell about Islam
to their community.
So the Messenger of God asked for safety.
He took a promise.
So that...
The lives of his companions can be safe.
And what happened next?
The hypocrites did what befits them.
When they arrived at the Ma'una's well...
...the fiercest army of infidels
was waiting for them.
Before they could say a word,
Hafizs were murdered.
Seventy Hafizs.
Seventy Quran lovers.
They fell martyr.
And when the news reached Medina...
...the hearts of the believers burned.
And they drowned in tears.
As for the hypocrites, they rejoiced.
The fire that burned the heart
of the Messenger of Allah...
...was such a scorching fire that...
Enes Bin Malik said he hadn't seen
the Messenger of Allah...
grieve over anything as much as
he grieves over his companions....
who were martyred at the well of Ma'una.
The Messenger of Allah, with the pain
in his heart,
...cursed the murderers of Hafizs...
...after every dawn prayer he performs.
He damned them.
I am surprised.
I thought he would have mercy on
them and pray for them
Mercy for the oppressor
is betrayal of the oppressed...
...Ismihan Sultan.
Such an unfortunate Hafizs.
Hafizs are martyr.
They received the prayer of the Prophet.
Why feel sorry for them?
All those educated people.
Moreover, they are companions to Prophet.
It is okay to be upset.
Do not be sad, Ismihan Sultan.
For us,
there is no higher rank than martyrdom.
However, fear that...
...fear for the possibility
to become a hypocrite.
In the name of of Allah
the Merciful the Compassionate
Fear that one may turn their back
on the truth and fall into contempt
The consequences of cruelty...
...are always miserable.
Marmarcik Castle.
They left me no other solution.
Who would want to crush
her mother and father's words?
No one would.
My Cicek.
(Cicek means flower)
My beautiful daughter.
Are you well?
Why would I not be okay, mother?
While you are in love with that boy...
...your father found it appropriate to
marry you to Bayindir.
I hope that doesn't make you sad.
My mother, my father and our Sultan
also found it appropriate.
Why would I be sad?
You make me happy.
What is wrong, my Cicek?
Where are you going?
I will not quit trading just because
I am going to marry, mother.
Business is waiting for me in the market.
Praise be to my daughter!
Off you go.
Go quickly and come back quickly.
Gokmen!
Tell Bayindir Bey.
His future wife will elope
with someone else.
Kantakouzanos is the sole heir to the throne.
We've blocked him twice.
But Andronicus is a fool.
Sooner or later,
Kantakouzanos will ascend the throne
And when he he does...
He will push the army towards Yenişehir.
The army...
...Bursa and Iznik,
they will stop here.
If we take over Kopru Hisar.
We'll create a line of defense here.
And if we can't conquer it...
Then we will not be able to
stop the army from attacking us.
Ismihan Hatun,
who think this is an opportunity for her...
...will damage us inside.
For this reason...
...this place is not just a conquest for us.
This is a matter of existance for us!
After the conquest of Marmaracik...
...the neighboring castles
increased their measures, my Bey.
All are in vain.
They will not be able to stand against us.
We will also increase our measures.
We'll, Cerkutay.
Konur, tell us about the news.
They are more than us in number, my Bey,
their walls are strong.
However, our discovery matches up
with Gürbüz Alp's information.
They have 5-toise (9 meters)
tall weak walls there.
They strengthened it, but it is not enough.
Konur.
You will approach them with five alps.
The walls will be lit with torches
Boran!
The catapults will shoot together.
And you'll blow a hole
in that wall on your first try.
A troop of alps will enter through that gap.
They will head for the gates
when they get inside.
When they open them...
...Alps and sister will start attacking.
Before the soldiers realise anything...
...we'll conquer Kopru Hisar Inshallah.
Insha'Allah
Bala, you'll be standing
behind those gates.
Konur, you'll lighten the walls.
Boran, and you will take care of
the catapults.
You'll manage the alps there.
And I'll be the first person
to get inside through that hole.
My Bey.
Our catapults and skillful
warriors are with Turgut Alp.
I don't want an excuse.
You will one shot there!
Otherwise, conquest fails.
Never forget that.
As you command my Bey.
When do we attack, Olof?
We'll wait for nightfall.
Darkness will fall upon them first,
and then us.
Is this going to end once
we destroy the headquarters, Olof?
Yes it will.
Because Turgut broke up with him.
Ismihan Sultan seperated them.
We will finish them.
Their important commander
is in the headquarters.
All siege weapons are in the headquarters.
When we destroy there...
...put conquering a castle aside...
...they won't even be able to
defend a town.
They are tattered inside and outside.
He is basically dead.
He just doesn't realize it.
Make preparations.
We'll stain Osman's camp with blood tonight.
We will answer the invitation
of Ismihan Hatun.
We are not willing to but we have to
play by their rules.
She will think we obey but...
...let her think that way.
Make preparations!
We'll start attacking
as soon as we get back.
Let's go.
Bala.
Why are you standing?
The camp must not be left empty, my Bey.
Our enemies are crowded.
I'd like to stay if you'll allow me.
Permission is yours, but take precautions.
When you are here,
I will not worry about here.
Go!
I am here Alcicek.
I am here.
Aktemur. Aktemur.
You did wrong to me Aktemur.
You will pay for it.
Alcicek is mine.
I cleaned up the trash between us,
Alcicek Hatun.
Where are you, Aktemur?
Where are you?
You're not going to
let hell swallow me, are you?
You won't do this to us.
You will come Aktemur.
You will come.
Mother.
Alcicek.
You...
Did this love blind your eyes, daughter?
How do you do this to us?
Mother.
He didn't come.
He didn't come, did he?
He won't come,
I knew it.
He will not come.
He didn't come, mother.
He didn't.
He left me alone.
Get up
Get up.
Is this fickle's vain love going to upset you?
You are my daughter.
Alcicek, you are strong.
You have to be strong.
Wipe away your tears.
It is a shame that you cry over a disloyal
man who left you alone.
Stand tall.
Well done my beautiful daughter.
Come on, let's go.
So you gave up on me!
Subasi.
So that's how much you love!
Sogut.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you
Attention, Hadrat Mother Sultan!
Welcome.
Thank you Ismihan Sultan.
This khan and Sogut are your inheritance
from your father Ertugrtul.
It's your right to sit on the main corner.
Please.
In the presence of Mother Sultan...
...I will sit wherever she wants me to sit.
Eyvallah.
Where is Bala Hatun?
We have many enemies.
We did not leave Yenişehir without leader.
Tell us.
Why did you invite us?
We haven't been able to talk in detail
since we came.
It has always been a chaos.
First, I have to say that...
...Konya is grateful for your presence,
Osman Bey.
Thank you, thank you.
Well, are the other tribes grateful
for Konya being here?
Sultan Mesut came and freed Geyhatu.
You came and freed Kantakuzenos.
Konya frees our enemies...
....whenever we capture them.
We've been through all these things
together, Osman Bey.
Sultan Masut saved you from the teeth
of a Mongol army.
Well, what about you Ismihan Sultan?
From whom did you save us?
The news of his daughter's death and
the news of Kantakuzenos' captivity...
...were given to Emperor Andranikos
at the same time.
With all his anger, he wrote this letter
to Konya.
Kantakouzanos shall be freed.
Or else...
An Army will attack Yenisehir.
Kantakouzanos is the sole heir to the throne.
That is, Konya has saved you from
a great calamity again, Malhun Hatun.
Moreover...
Kantakouzanos is the one
who will sit on the throne from now on.
You are wrong, Ismihan Sultan.
The emperor is sick.
Kantakouzanos is sitting on the throne
temporarily.
Constantine
Emperor's Palace
Throne, you finally met your true friend.
Soon you will be completely mine.
When that sick Andronicus dies.
You shall be mine as I am the sole heir.
The rule of cowards will end.
By my light, Byzantium will be resurrected.
I will kill Osman and all the Turks.
Be ready.
Byzantium will bring you hell.
What's gone is gone.
I'm coming for what's left in your hands,
Osman.
For what's left in your hands.
Are you still crying?
Maybe he came after we left, mother.
I had to wait.
He said he would come.
But he didn't come, Alcicek!
He was afraid of Bayindir Bey and
Ismihan Sultan.
He gave up on you at the first difficulty.
You have to understand.
Your love and Aktemur's love are not equal.
Don't cry anymore.
I can't stop it.
My tears drop.
Sometimes you can't resist.
You know people go no matter
what you do to stop them.
Like I did.
I didn't stop you even though
I knew you'd try to elope.
Why?
You are my daughter.
You wouldn't stop before
doing what you want to do.
I wish you had stopped me, mother.
I wish you had stopped me.
So that I wouldn't go through this.
Let your heart burn.
This pain will not let you forget
the lesson you learned.
You had a dream, my daughter.
You just woke up from this dream.
Aktemur is a temporary obsession.
If you had married him, you would be only
a wife of Subasi. Nothing more.
But Bayindir Bey is different.
Ismihan Sultan supports him.
You think about the present,
I think about the future.
My beautiful daughter.
You will not shed tears for someone who
abandoned you and left you behind.
You will destroy if anyone crushes you!
Mother...
You're a sensible girl, Alcicek.
Act with your head, not your heart.
From now on, I will listen to you.
I will marry Bayindir Bey.
Let's go!
Bala Hatun is coming!
Alps!
Sisters!
We deployed our valiants
in front of Kopru Hisar.
Once we attack at dawn,
they'll start the attack there as well.
Valiants of Kayi!
Valiant Hatuns!
Let the blue sky split open and the
black earth split open!
Let the swords of justice
we carry come out of their sheaths!
May our conquest be blessed!
- Amen!
Konur Alp!
Get the catapults ready.
You will arrive at the walls before dawn.
Your command, Bala Hatun.
Come on, my brothers!
It's time.
Only the smell of death will
spread tonight.
Alps!
Raid!
Get in the position!
Now!
Catapults.
You dog!
Who will save you from my hands now?
Who?
Everything will be flattened!
Everything!
Attack!
You want to finish yourself huh?
Come on then.
Come on!
Game of thrones and rulers.
I hope Kantakouzanos doesn't make
a mistake to us, for the sake of our alliance.
Peace will come, Osman Bey.
Of course, only if you don't make
a counter strike.
We are not the ones who want peace.
We're just giving a break.
However...
If Mother Sultan wants peace...
...it is a must to obey her.
I am grateful to you.
I hope you're not upset about
Alcicek issue.
Good deeds require fast happening.
We didn't know you wanted her.
There is no certainty about anything.
Everything is about destiny.
We wish the best.
This is the best.
By the way, my son Sultan Aladdin...
...send a lot of gifts to Aladdin because
he has the same.
He gifted the most beautiful horse to
the son who is going to be a Bey.
And the sharpest sword for Orhan.
To use it to protect his Bey.
Thank you Mother Sultan.
Sons.
Check the gifts given by Mother Sultan.
I see that you decided which son to
be the heir of the throne, Ismihan Sultan.
Not at all, Malhun Hatun.
I say that for you.
This is a custom in Kayi tribe.
The little ones sit on the throne.
And the big brothers protect them.
That's what we heard.
Our men have chased
this horse for years.
It took a long time to catch him.
When Sultan Aladdin heard your name...
...he wanted to gift him to you, Aladdin Bey.
Really, it's very beautiful.
I will write a letter of gratitude
to Sultan, Avci Bey.
It's very beautiful, brother.
What are you going to call him?
His name is...
Akyel.
Praise be! Praise be!
So brother...
What are you going to name your sword?
I'll call it a game breaker, brother.
Don't worry Aladdin Bey.
I'll arrange a saddle.
You must be wondering why
we haven't started eating yet.
Because we have another guest.
Peace be upon you.
And may peace be upon you.
And may peace be upon you
You will die, snake!
I swear you will die!
Don't waste your breath in vain.
We breathe for martyrdom.
My Allah, give me strength!
It's your end now, snake!
Olof!
I will kill you.
I will put Osman in a great pain.
You will not run away from your end.
Say what you're going to say quickly.
Correct.
No need to prolong it.
You should know that we are at the same page
with Ismihan Sultan now.
There is no doubt about this.
Who does not seek power?
Who doesn't want a throne?
Your absence in our way..
...lessens only you...
...not our way.
I did not stray from the way.
Why would you say that?
Even if the path is different,
the goal is the same!
Do not consider us your enemies
because we do not follow you
No Osman Bey.
If anything happens to my people...
...because you left...
You will pay for it with your head.
No one will be beheaded, Osman Bey.
Peace and order will be secured
under the rule of the Seljuk state.
In the existence of the state, no one shall
do the state business!
Ismihan Sultan.
Olof attacked a Turkish headquarters
near Kopru Hisar.
The situation is dangerous.
Who is this Osman Bey?
Who established headquarters
in front of Kopru Hisar?
The headquarters is mine.
The command is mine.
And I decide whose head will be cut off.
Please contact turkision@gmail.com for any inquiries